Asher Kim

Full-Stack (Or Back End) Web Developer, Entry-Level

asherkim815@gmail.com Seoul, South Korea

Summary

I am confident I will be valuable to your company for three reasons:

1. I have history of great teamwork

All teams I belonged to achieved great results. My team won new employee product idea competition at CJ CheilJedang, collegiate baseball club won 2nd place in national tournament, collegiate classical guitar club won 1st place in national competition, and more. By putting team above me and doing what team needs, even if I don't like it, I believe I contributed to each team's success.

- 2. I tailor my work to customer and employer
 I ran e-commerce business for two years, and though I failed, I experienced being
 business owner. I will work from customer's and employer's perspectives, not mine.
- 3. I will grow quickly as developer It's likely I will make performing developer for two reasons. First, I fit programming. I enjoy spending time thinking and solving difficult problems. At school, people sought me for one reason: math problems. Second, I learn fast. One of my Gallup strengths is Input: gathering and soaking in new information. I will learn what you require (e.g. tech stacks) and adapt to work environment swiftly.

Experience

Overseas Sales Representative

2017.07 - 2019.03

North America Team, Overseas Sales Department, CJ CheilJedang Seoul, South Korea

- Managed key food products' export to North America, and helped NA team exceed goal by 5-20% every quarter
- Elicited good cooperation from involved departments (Marketing, Packaging, Quality, SCM, Production, and more) by always communicating with humility, rare behavior in company's competitive culture
- Increased involved departments' performances by voluntarily devising and doing needed work. Organized weekly spreadsheets containing key products' orders, inventory, and production dates. Shared with SCM and Production, helped them make effective schedule adjustments, and prevented almost 100% of stockouts. Had more personal workload but decreased others' (e.g. stopped feuds and negotiations among Overseas Sales teams that arose from stockouts).

Military Interpreter 2009.07 - 2011.05
Republic of Korea Army Seoul, South Korea

Contributed to successful ROK-US joint exercise as senior translator

Education

BA in English (Linguistics & Literature) 2013.03 - 2017.02 Hanyang University Seoul, South Korea

Minutiae

- Enjoys using brain to beat difficult video games (e.g. devising builds in Monster Hunter and Dark Souls to beat hard bosses)
- · As introvert, prefers balancing socializing with bit more solitude

Portfolio

asherkim815.github.io/ personal-website/

Skills

Non-Languages:

- React
- Node
- Express
- Passport (OAuth, etc.)
- PostgreSQL

Languages:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- SQL

Courses

- CS50x
- Data Analysis

Languages

- English Proficient
- Korean Native

Awards

1st Place, New Employee Product Idea Competition

- Team Leader
- CJ CheilJedang, 2017